printavo.com 2019-03-08

# 

### Privacy Policy

**1\. Introduction**  
Protecting your private information is our priority. We are committed to respect and protect the privacy of both Customers and Customer End Users and the information we may obtain through the Service and/or the Site, and we have created this Privacy Policy to inform all Users about how we collect, use and share Customer personal information and that of Customer End Users, and about our privacy practices in general.

**2\. Definitions**  
Throughout this document, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand the meaning of them. The following is a non-exhaustive list of definitions of words and phrases found in this document:

“Customer” refers to those persons or entities that have contracted with Printavo to use the Services with Customer End Users.

“Customer End Users” refers to those clients and/or end users of the applicable Customer.

"Printavo" refers to our company, known as "Printavo, Inc"; our Site; our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context in which the word is used;

"Service" refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including our customer insight services and our Site itself;

"Site" refers to our website, www.Printavo.com;

"User" refers to anyone who uses our Service, including Customers, Customer End Users, and general visitors to our Site;

"You" refers to you, the person who is governed by this Privacy Policy.

**3\. Information Collected**  
Identifying Information  
We collect certain personal information from Customers when a Customer signs up to our Service that can be used to identify you, such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, telephone number, and any other information that we deem relevant for the purpose of providing you with our Service or which you provided to use voluntarily. The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.

As you navigate the Service, we may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as cookies and web beacons (“Web Site Navigational Information”). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Service (such as the web pages viewed and the links clicked).

Through our import process, we may also collect information provided by Customers, such as the name, company name, address, phone number, email address, revenue, account data, etc of Customer End Users that you choose to share with us. When you provide us with personal information about your Customer End Users, we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided, such as to add new records to your account, or as agreed in the applicable agreement with Customer.

Non-Identifying Information  
Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider. Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

**4\. Use of Your Information**  
We may use your information to:  
Enhance or improve User experience, our Site, or our Service.  
Process transactions.  
Send e-mails about our Site or respond to inquiries.  
Send e-mails and updates about Printavo, including our e-mail newsletters.  
Perform any other function that we believe in good faith is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service.

**5\. Customer End Users**  
As part of the provision of the Service to Customers, Printavo collects certain information and data about Customer End Users as determined by the applicable Customer (“Customer End User Data”). Printavo does not control or otherwise approve any messages or requests for Customer End User Data made by a Customer to a Customer End User. Customer End Users should be aware that a Customer can request such Customer End User Data from them in order to use the Customer’s products or services and that Customer End User Data may then be included in information given to Printavo or through your use of the Service. Therefore, Customer End Users should review the privacy policy of a Customer’s applicable product or service to assess the security of any information a Customer End User discloses. To the extent that Printavo receives any Customer End User Data, Printavo shall make reasonable efforts, consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy, to maintain the confidentiality of such Customer End User Data. Printavo has no direct relationship to the Customer End Users whose Customer End User Data it processes and such Customer End User who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate Customer End User Data should direct such query to the applicable Customer for removal. Once such Customer requests removal of such applicable Customer End User Data, Printavo will respond to such request within one month; provided that (i) such period may be extended by up to two additional months when necessary, taking into account the complexity and number of the requests and (ii) Printavo shall inform you of any such extension within one month of receipt of the request, together with the reasons for the delay.

**6\. Customer End User Data**  
Printavo’s Customers may electronically submit Customer End User Data. Printavo will not review, share, distribute, or reference any such Customer End User Data except as provided in Printavo’s applicable agreement with Customer, or as may be required by law. Printavo acknowledges that Customer End Users have the right to access their personal information. If personal information pertaining to a Customer End User has been submitted to us by a Customer and a Customer End User wishes to exercise any rights it may have to access, correct, amend, or delete such data, Customer End User should inquire with the Customer directly. Because Printavo personnel have limited ability to access data our Customers submit to the Service, if a Customer End User wishes to make a request directly to Printavo, please provide the name of the Customer who submitted your data to the Service. We will refer your request to such Customer and will support them as needed in responding to your request.

**7\. Data Controller and Data Processor; Data Protection Officer**  
We process personal data both as a Processor and as a Controller, each as defined in the EU Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 (the “Directive”) and the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”). The Customer which Customer End Users provided personal data to, with the assistance of the Service, will be the Controller for Customer End User Data. We will be the Processor of Customer End User Data. For Customer personal data, we will be the Controller.

Printavo has a Data Protection Officer (as defined in the Directive and GDPR) who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. Our Data Protection Officer can be reached as follows:

Printavo, Inc.  
Attn: Data Protection Officer  
321 N Clark St., #2550  
Chicago, IL 60654  
support@printavo.com

**8\. Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information**  
Customers may in some cases be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided to us by logging into your account on the Site and editing their account. Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache. We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such. In addition, we may, from time to time, retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database.

**9\. Cookies**  
We use cookies to create a session and remember a User as they use our Site, in order to distinguish them from other Users. This provides additional security and convenience beyond simply identifying Users based on their IP address, since more than one User can share the same address. For this reason, it is necessary that you enable cookies in your browser, and you hereby acknowledge that we have informed you of our use of cookies and that you consent to our use of cookies in relation to your computer system.

**10\. Third Party Websites**  
Printavo may post links to third party websites on its Site. These third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by Printavo, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site. Printavo bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website. Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.

**11\. Third Party Access to Your Information**  
Although you are entering into an Agreement with Printavo to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.

Throughout the course of our provision of our Service to you, we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information. For example, our web host stores the information that you provide us, and we may hire outside contractors to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy. For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems. You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you authorize us to collect, store, share, and otherwise use your information in conjunction with:  
Google Analytics  
Intercom  
MailChimp  
Amazon Web Services  
Heroku  
AttributionApp  
CloseIo  
Elasticsearch  
Stripe  
Google AdWords

**12\. Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes**  
At times it may become necessary or desirable, for legal purposes, to release your information in response to a request from a government agency or a private litigant. You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matter. In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either. We may also proactively report you, and release your information to, third parties where we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities. You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.

**13\. Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications**  
By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communications with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited e-mails from Printavo since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communications from us or anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy. However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying Printavo that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database.

**14\. Security Measures**  
We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, including using SSL certificates and vulnerability scanning. However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information. It is in our interest to keep our Site secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

**15\. Your California Privacy Rights**  
Printavo permits residents of the State of California to use its Service. Therefore, it is the intent of Printavo to comply with the California Business and Professions Code §§ 22575-22579. If you are a California resident you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes. In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors. You may contact us at support@printavo.com with any questions.

**16\. International Transfer**  
Your information may be transferred to—and maintained on—computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, Printavo transfers Personal Information to the United States and processes it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer, subject to any applicable provisions of this Privacy Policy.

**17\. Amendments**  
We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our privacy practices. All Users, including Customers and Customer End Users, are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy periodically and to check the “Last Updated” date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy for the most recent version. If we make changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, the Service or the Site.

**18\. EU-U.S. Privacy**  
Printavo complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Printavo has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Printavo, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Private Shield policy should first contact Printavo, Inc. at: support@printavo.com

Printavo Inc. has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint. The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

Printavo is responsible for the processing of Personal Information it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. We comply with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In the event that personal information is (i) to be disclosed to a third party that is not acting as an agent to perform task(s) on behalf of and under the instructions of Printavo or (ii) to be used for a purpose that is materially different from the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized, you may opt out by contacting us at support@printavo.com.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider TRUSTe (free of charge to you) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request .

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

Last Modified: May 21, 2018
